Guide to the Gerald H. Anderson Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Writings, Lectures, Research Files, 1957-2012; Series II
  - Regarding booklength works
    - Biographical Dictionary of Christian Mission
      - Authors File
        - Malatesta, Edward, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 260)
        - Markussen, Flemming, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 261)
        - Masson, Joseph, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 262)
        - Mathews, James K., 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 263)
        - McCarthy, William D., n.d. (Box 2, Folder 264)
        - McClung, Grant, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 265)
        - McComish, Margaret, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 266)
        - McConville, William E., 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 267)
        - McGee, Gary B., 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 268)
        - McGraw, Gerald E., n.d. (Box 3, Folder 269)
        - McGreal, Mary N., 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 270)
        - McIntosh, Stuart, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 271)
        - McKinley, Edward H., 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 272)
        - Metzler, Josef, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 273)
        - Michell, David J., 1993 (Box 3, Folder 274)
        - Min, Ma, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 275)
        - Minkema, Kenneth, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 276)
        - Mitchell, William, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 277)
        - Moffett, Eileen, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 278)
        - Moffett, Samuel, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 279)
        - Monet, Jacques, 1993-1997 (Box 3, Folder 280)
        - Motte, Mary M., 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 281)
        - Muller, Karl, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 282)
        - Mousalimas, S.A., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 283)
        - Mulholland, Kenneth, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 284)
        - Muller, Klaus, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 285)
        - Murray, Jocelyn, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 286)
        - Murray, Graeme, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 287)
        - Mugello, David E., 1995 (Box 3, Folder 288)
        - Mykelbust, Olav G., n.d. (Box 3, Folder 289)
        - Myhre, Paul O., 1996 (Box 3, Folder 290)
        - Neely, Alan, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 291)
        - Newbigin, Lesslie, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 292)
        - Ng, Peter, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 293)
        - Nichols, Aidan, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 294)
        - Nikkel, Marc, 1993-1997 (Box 3, Folder 295)
        - Njoroge, Nyambura J., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 296)
        - Noort, Gerrit, 1994-1997 (Box 3, Folder 297)
        - Noll, Craig A., 1995 (Box 3, Folder 298)
        - Noll, Mark A., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 299)
        - Norbeck, Mark D., 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 300)
        - Norris, Frederick W., 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 301)
        - Nunnenmacher, Eugen, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 302)
        - O'Connor, Daniel, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 303)
        - O'Malley, John S., 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 304)
        - O'Malley, John, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 305)
        - O'Neill, Charles, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 306)
        - Oda, Vianney Takehiko, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 307)
        - O'Shea, Michael, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 308)
        - Ojo, Matthews A., 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 309)
        - Ok, Chun Chae, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 310)
        - Oleksa, Michael, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 311)
        - Oleksa, Michael, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 312)
        - Oosthuizen, G.C., 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 313)
        - Orr, Rodney, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 314)
        - Padilla, C. Rene, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 315)
        - Parrott, John, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 316)
        - Partee, Charles, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 317)
        - Patterson, James A., 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 318)
        - Peel, J.D.Y., 1995 (Box 3, Folder 319)
        - Peelman, Achiel, 1993-1997 (Box 3, Folder 320)
        - Pelikan, Jaroslav, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 321)
        - Penner, Peter, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 322)
        - Perry, Cindy, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 323)
        - Peterson, Stephen, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 324)
        - Phillips, James, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 325)
        - Pierard, Richard V., 1993-1997 (Box 3, Folder 326)
        - Pickard, William, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 327)
        - Piggin, Stuart, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 328)
        - Pierson, Paul, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 329)
        - Pirouet, Louise, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 330)
        - Piryns, Ernest D., n.d. (Box 3, Folder 331)
        - Pobee, John S., 1993-1997 (Box 3, Folder 332)
        - Prang, Margaret, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 333)
        - Presbyterian/History (Ross, Kenneth J.), 1996 (Box 3, Folder 334)
        - Poitras, Edward W., 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 335)
        - Rader, Lyell M., 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 336)
        - Rabassa, Gregory, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 337)
        - Rader, Paul A., 1995 (Box 3, Folder 338)
        - Ranger, Terrence O., 1993 (Box 3, Folder 339)
        - Ranjeva, Yvette, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 340)
        - Raupp, Werner, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 341)
        - Reapsome, James W., 1993 (Box 3, Folder 342)
        - Reapsome, James, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 343)
        - Reavis, Ralph, 1993-1997 (Box 3, Folder 344)
        - Rees, D. Ben, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 345)
        - Reid, Daniel G., 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 346)
        - Riggans, Walter, 1993-1997 (Box 3, Folder 347)
        - Robert, Dana, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 348)
        - Roberts, W. Dayton, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 349)
        - Rodgers, Peter, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 350)
        - Roest Crollius, Arij, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 351)
        - Rollman, Hans-Josef, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 352)
        - Rooy, Sidney, 1993-1997 (Box 3, Folder 353)
        - Ross, H. Miriam, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 354)
        - Ross, Andrew C., 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 355)
        - Ross, Theodore, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 356)
        - Rouner, Leroy, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 357)
        - Roxborough, John, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 358)
        - Rowdon, Herold, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 359)
        - Rubingh, Eugene, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 360)
        - Ruokanen, Mikka, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 361)
        - Russell, Beryl, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 362)
        - Rzepkowski, Horst, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 363)
        - Saayman, Willem, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 364)
        - Samarin, William, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 365)
        - Sanneh, Lamin, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 366)
        - Samarin, William, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 367)
        - Samartha, S.J., 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 368)
        - Schattschneider, David, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 369)
        - Scherer, James, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 370)
        - Schreiner, Lothar, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 371)
        - Schreiter, Robert J., 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 372)
        - Schumacher, John N., 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 373)
        - Scott, Robert, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 374)
        - Scott, William Henry, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 375)
        - Seamands, J.T., 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 376)
        - Shank, David A., 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 377)
        - Sharpe, Eric J., 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 378)
        - Shaull, Richard, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 379)
        - Shenk, Wilbert R., 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 380)
        - Shepperson, George, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 381)
        - Shorter, Aylward, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 382)
        - Showalter, Nathan D, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 383)
        - Sider, E. Morris, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 384)
        - Sinclair, John H., 1993 (Box 4, Folder 385)
        - Sitompul, A.A., 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 386)
        - Skarsaune, Oskar, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 387)
        - Slate, C. Philip, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 388)
        - Smalley, Martha Lund, 1993-1997 (Box 4, Folder 389)
        - Smalley, William, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 390)
        - Smith, A. Christopher, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 391)
        - Smith, Charles E., 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 392)
        - Smith, David, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 393)
        - Soderlund, Linnea, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 394)
        - Souza, Teotonio de, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 395)
        - Spence, Jonathan, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 396)
        - Spindler, M.R., 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 397)
        - Stamoolis, James, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 398)
        - Stanley, Brian, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 399)
        - Staples, Russell, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 400)
        - Starkloff, Carl, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 401)
        - Steiner, Evgeny, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 402)
        - Stevenson, Nancy, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 403)
        - Stine, Philip, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 404)
        - Stockwell, Eugene, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 405)
        - Stott, John, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 406)
        - Stout, Harry, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 407)
        - Stowe, David M., 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 408)
        - Sugden, Chris, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 409)
        - Sundermeier, Theo, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 410)
        - Sunquist, Scott W., 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 411)
        - Svelmoe, William, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 412)
        - Swain, Terry (Tony?), 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 413)
        - Swai, Lal, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 414)
        - Taber, Charles R., 1993 (Box 4, Folder 415)
        - Thangaraj, M. Thomas, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 416)
        - Taylor, John V., 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 417)
        - Thelle, Notto R., 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 418)
        - Thomas, Norman E., 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 419)
        - Thompson, Jack, 1993-1997 (Box 4, Folder 420)
        - Thornton, John, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 421)
        - Toews, Paul E., 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 422)
        - Torjessen, Ed, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 423)
        - Tienou, Tite, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 424)
        - Torrance, T.F., 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 425)
        - Trompf, Gary, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 426)
        - Tucker, Ruth A., 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 427)
        - Tuggy, Leonard, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 428)
        - Turner, Harold W., 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 429)
        - Turner, Philip, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 430)
        - Underwood, Horace G., 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 431)
        - Ustorf, Werner, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 432)
        - Valerie, Mark, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 433)
        - van Asselt, Willem J., 1994 (Box 4, Folder 434)
        - Van der Bent Ans, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 435)
        - Van der Heyden, Ulrich, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 436)
        - Van Engen, Charles, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 437)
        - Van Oort, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 438)
        - Van Schwalwyk, Annalet, 1994-1997 (Box 4, Folder 439)
        - Verkuyl, Joh., n.d. (Box 4, Folder 440)
        - Vickers, John, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 441)
        - Verstraelen, Frans J., n.d. (Box 4, Folder 442)
        - Vikner, David W., 1995 (Box 4, Folder 443)
        - Walls, Andrew, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 444)
        - Ward, Kevin, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 445)
        - Weber, Charles W., 1994 (Box 4, Folder 446)
        - Webster, John C.B., 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 447)
        - West, Charles, 1993-1997 (Box 4, Folder 448)
        - Whaling, Frank, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 449)
        - White, Gavin, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 450)
        - Whiteman, Darrell, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 451)
        - Wiest, Jean-Paul, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 452)
        - Williams, Peter, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 453)
        - Williams, Walter L., 1993 (Box 4, Folder 454)
        - Willeke, Bernward, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 455)
        - Witek, John, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 456)
        - Wills, David, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 457)
        - Wilson, Dorothy Clarke, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 458)
        - Wilson, Everett A., 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 459)
        - Witteveen, K.M., 1994 (Box 4, Folder 460)
        - Wolcott, Kevin, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 461)
        - Wong, K.M., 1995 (Box 4, Folder 462)
        - Wong, Timothy Man-Kong, 1995-1997 (Box 4, Folder 463)
        - Yates, T.E., 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 464)
        - Yuhaus, Cassian, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 465)
        - Zamuel, Hesdie, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 466)
        - Young, Betty, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 467)
        - Yung, Hwa, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 468)
        - Zikmund, Barbara Brown, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 469)
        - Zorn, Jean-Francois, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 470)
      - Articles File
        - Index to Articles (Box 5, Folder 471)
        - Abdul, Masih (Box 5, Folder 472)
        - Abeel, David (Box 5, Folder 473)
        - Abel, Charles William (Box 5, Folder 474)
        - Abraham, Samuel (Box 5, Folder 475)
        - Abraham, Mar Thoma (Box 5, Folder 476)
        - Abrams, Minnie F. (Box 5, Folder 477)
        - Acosta, Jose de (Box 5, Folder 478)
        - Adalbert (Box 5, Folder 479)
        - Adalbert of Bremen (Box 5, Folder 480)
        - Adalbert of Prague, Bohemia (Box 5, Folder 481)
        - Adam, William (Box 5, Folder 482)
        - Addai (and Aggai) (Box 5, Folder 483)
        - Adejobi, Emmanuel (Adeleke) (Box 5, Folder 484)
        - Adeney, David (Box 5, Folder 485)
        - Adriani, Nicolaus (Box 5, Folder 486)
        - Agebi, Majola (David Brown Vincent) (Box 5, Folder 487)
        - Aea, Hezekiah and Debora (Box 5, Folder 488)
        - Affonso, Mvemba-Nzinga (Box 5, Folder 489)
        - Agnew, Eliza (Box 5, Folder 490)
        - Aggrey, James Emman Kwegvir (Box 5, Folder 491)
        - Ahui, John (Box 5, Folder 492)
        - Aidan (Box 5, Folder 493)
        - Aina, J. Ade (Box 5, Folder 494)
        - Aitolos, Cosmas (Box 5, Folder 495)
        - Akinyele, Isaac Babalola (Box 5, Folder 496)
        - Akrofi (Box 5, Folder 497)
        - Aldersey, Mary Ann (Box 5, Folder 498)
        - Aleni, Guido (Box 5, Folder 499)
        - Alexander, Michael Solomon (Box 5, Folder 500)
        - Alexander, William Patterson (Box 5, Folder 501)
        - Alexander VI (Rodrigo Borja [Borgia]) (Box 5, Folder 502)
        - Ali, Wallay'at (Box 5, Folder 503)
        - Allamano, Giuseppe (Box 5, Folder 504)
        - Allan, George and Mary (Sterling) (Box 5, Folder 505)
        - Allen, George (Box 5, Folder 506)
        - Allen, David Oliver (Box 5, Folder 507)
        - Allen, Horace Newton (Box 5, Folder 508)
        - Allen, Roland (Box 5, Folder 509)
        - Allen, Young John (Box 5, Folder 510)
        - Alli, Jahni (Box 5, Folder 511)
        - Allier, Raoul (Box 5, Folder 512)
        - Allouez, Claude Jean (Box 5, Folder 513)
        - Allshorn, Florence (Box 5, Folder 514)
        - Alopen (Box 5, Folder 515)
        - Altham, John (Box 5, Folder 516)
        - Alzina, Ignacio (Box 5, Folder 517)
        - Amadeus, (Mother) Mary (Box 5, Folder 518)
        - Amalorpavadass, D.S. (Box 5, Folder 519)
        - Amandus (Box 5, Folder 520)
        - Ambrazis, Nicholas (Box 5, Folder 521)
        - Amiot, Joseph Maria (Box 5, Folder 522)
        - Ambrosius (Box 5, Folder 523)
        - Amu, Ephraim (Box 5, Folder 524)
        - Anawati, Georges (Box 5, Folder 525)
        - Anastasius (Box 5, Folder 526)
        - Anchieta, Jose de (Box 5, Folder 527)
        - Anderson, Christopher (Box 5, Folder 528)
        - Anderson, David (Box 5, Folder 529)
        - Anderson, James Norman D. (Box 5, Folder 530)
        - Anderson, John (Box 5, Folder 531)
        - Anderson, Louisa (Peterswald) (Box 5, Folder 532)
        - Anderson, William and Louisa (Box 5, Folder 533)
        - Anderson, William H. (Box 5, Folder 534)
        - Anderson, William (Box 5, Folder 535)
        - Anderson, Rufus (Box 5, Folder 536)
        - Andrade, Antonio de (Box 5, Folder 537)
        - Andre, Louis (Box 5, Folder 538)
        - Andrew of Perugia (Box 5, Folder 539)
        - Andrews, Charles Freer (Box 5, Folder 540)
        - Andrews, Lorrin (Box 5, Folder 541)
        - Andrianaivoravelona (Box 5, Folder 542)
        - Anskar (Ansgar) (Box 5, Folder 543)
        - Anselm (Box 5, Folder 544)
        - Anthing, FL (Box 5, Folder 545)
        - Anzer, Johann Baptist (von) (Box 5, Folder 546)
        - Appasamy, Aiyadurai Jesudasen (Box 5, Folder 547)
        - Appenzeller, Henry Gerhart (Box 5, Folder 548)
        - Aquaviva, Rodolfo (Box 5, Folder 549)
        - Aquinas, Thomas (Box 5, Folder 550)
        - Arbousset, Thomas (Box 5, Folder 551)
        - Archbell, James (Box 5, Folder 552)
        - Arias, Mortimer (Box 5, Folder 553)
        - Armstrong, Philip E. (Box 5, Folder 554)
        - Armstrong, Annie (Box 5, Folder 555)
        - Armstrong, Richard (Box 5, Folder 556)
        - Armstrong, William F. (Box 5, Folder 557)
        - Arnot, Frederick Stanley (Box 5, Folder 558)
        - Armstrong, Hannah Maria Norris (Box 5, Folder 559)
        - Ao, Longri (Box 5, Folder 560)
        - Arriaga, Pablo Jose (Box 5, Folder 561)
        - Arrupe, Pedro (Box 5, Folder 562)
        - Arthington, Robert (Box 5, Folder 563)
        - Arthur, John W. (Box 5, Folder 564)
        - Arsenius of Koli (Box 5, Folder 565)
        - Arthur, John W. (Box 5, Folder 566)
        - Asbury, Francis (Box 5, Folder 567)
        - Ashmore, William (Box 5, Folder 568)
        - Atiman, Adrian (Box 5, Folder 569)
        - Atkinson, Maria W. (Box 5, Folder 570)
        - Auca, Five (Box 5, Folder 571)
        - Auer, John Gottlieb (Box 5, Folder 572)
        - Aufhauser, Johannes (Box 5, Folder 573)
        - Augouard, Prosper (Box 5, Folder 574)
        - Augustine, of Canterbury (Box 5, Folder 575)
        - Augustine, of Hippo (Box 5, Folder 576)
        - Auna (Box 5, Folder 577)
        - Avison, Oliver R. (Box 5, Folder 578)
        - Axenfeld, Karl (Box 5, Folder 579)
        - Axling, William (Box 5, Folder 580)
        - Aylward, Gladys (Box 5, Folder 581)
        - Azariah, Vedanaiakam (Box 5, Folder 582)
        - Azevedo, Ignacio de (Box 5, Folder 583)
        - Babalola, Joseph (Box 6, Folder 584)
        - Bach, T.J. (Box 6, Folder 585)
        - Bachmann, Traugott (Box 6, Folder 586)
        - Bacon, Sumner (Box 6, Folder 587)
        - Baedeker, Frederick William (Box 6, Folder 588)
        - Baeta, Christian Goncalves Kwami (Box 6, Folder 589)
        - Baez-Camargo, Gonzalo (Box 6, Folder 590)
        - Bagby, William B. (Box 6, Folder 591)
        - Bailey, Wellesley Cosby (Box 6, Folder 592)
        - Baird, Pierre (Box 6, Folder 593)
        - Baird, William M., Sr. (Box 6, Folder 594)
        - Baker, Amelia Dorothea (Kohlhoff) (Box 6, Folder 595)
        - Bakker, Dirk (Box 6, Folder 596)
        - Baldaeus, Philippus (Box 6, Folder 597)
        - Baldwin, Elizabeth and Jane (Box 6, Folder 598)
        - Ball, Dyer (Box 6, Folder 599)
        - Ball, Henry Cleophas (Box 6, Folder 600)
        - Ballantine, Henry (Box 6, Folder 601)
        - Ballantine, Henry (Box 6, Folder 602)
        - Baller, F.W. (Box 6, Folder 603)
        - Banerjea, Krishna Mohan (Box 6, Folder 604)
        - Bang, Ji El (Box 6, Folder 605)
        - Baradaeus, Jacob (Bar'Adai) (Box 6, Folder 606)
        - Baraga, Friedrich (Box 6, Folder 607)
        - Barber, Margaret (Box 6, Folder 608)
        - Barclay, Thomas (Box 6, Folder 609)
        - Barlow, Arthur Ruffless (Box 6, Folder 610)
        - Barratt, Thomas Ball (Box 6, Folder 611)
        - Barreira, Balthasar (Box 6, Folder 612)
        - Barreto, Joao Nunes (Box 6, Folder 613)
        - Barsumas (Bar Sauma) (Box 6, Folder 614)
        - Bartel, Henry Cornelius (Box 6, Folder 615)
        - Barzaeus (Barzaus), Kaspar (Box 6, Folder 616)
        - Barzana, Alonso de (Box 6, Folder 617)
        - Barth, Christian Gottlob (Box 6, Folder 618)
        - Barth, Karl (Box 6, Folder 619)
        - Bartlett, Reginald (Box 6, Folder 620)
        - Barton, James Levi (Box 6, Folder 621)
        - Barton, John (Box 6, Folder 622)
        - Bashford, James Whitford (Box 6, Folder 623)
        - Bataillon, Pierre-Marie (Box 6, Folder 624)
        - Bates, M(iner) Searle (Box 6, Folder 625)
        - Bavnick, Johan Herman (Box 6, Folder 626)
        - Baughman, Burr (Box 6, Folder 627)
        - Bax, Jacques (Box 6, Folder 628)
        - Baxter, Richard (Box 6, Folder 629)
        - Baynes, Alfred Henry (Box 6, Folder 630)
        - Beach, Harlan Page (Box 6, Folder 631)
        - Beaver, Robert Pierce (Box 6, Folder 632)
        - Becker, Carl (Box 6, Folder 633)
        - Becker, Edmund Christopher (Box 6, Folder 634)
        - Beckmann, Johannes (Box 6, Folder 635)
        - Bede (Box 6, Folder 636)
        - Bellavin, Tikhon (Box 6, Folder 637)
        - Belcourt, George Antoine (Box 6, Folder 638)
        - Belksma, J. (Box 6, Folder 639)
        - Bell, Lemuel Nelson (Box 6, Folder 640)
        - Benavides, Miguel de (Box 6, Folder 641)
        - Bender, Carl Jacob (Box 6, Folder 642)
        - Benedict (Box 6, Folder 643)
        - Benedict XIV (Prospero Lorenzo Lambertini) (Box 6, Folder 644)
        - Benedict XV (Giacomo della Chiesa) (Box 6, Folder 645)
        - Benignus, Pierre (Box 6, Folder 646)
        - Bennett, Belle Harris (Box 6, Folder 647)
        - Bennett, Cephas (Box 6, Folder 648)
        - Berg, Daniel (Box 6, Folder 649)
        - Benlloch y Vivo, Juan (Box 6, Folder 650)
        - Bentley, William Holman (Box 6, Folder 651)
        - Bergmann, Lorenz (Box 6, Folder 652)
        - Bergmann, Wilhelm (Box 6, Folder 653)
        - Berkeley, Xavier (Agnes Mary) (Box 6, Folder 654)
        - Bermyn (Bermijn), Alphons (Box 6, Folder 655)
        - Bernard-Maitre, Henri (Box 6, Folder 656)
        - Bernadino, Ignazio d'Asti (Box 6, Folder 657)
        - Barron, Paul (Box 6, Folder 658)
        - Bessieux, Jean Remi (Box 6, Folder 659)
        - Berthoud, Paul (Box 6, Folder 660)
        - Beschi, Constanzo Guisenne (Box 6, Folder 661)
        - Besson, Pablo (Box 6, Folder 662)
        - Betanzos, Domingo de (Box 6, Folder 663)
        - Bettelheim, Bernard J. (Box 6, Folder 664)
        - Bettendorf, Johann Philipp (Box 6, Folder 665)
        - Beyzym, Jan (Box 6, Folder 666)
        - Biard, Pierre (Box 6, Folder 666a)
        - Bibliander, Theodor (Box 6, Folder 667)
        - Bickel, Luke Washington (Box 6, Folder 668)
        - Bickersteth, Edward (Box 6, Folder 669)
        - Bickersteth, Edward (1850-1897) (Box 6, Folder 670)
        - Bicknell, Henry (Box 6, Folder 671)
        - Bieder, Werner (Box 6, Folder 672)
        - Bigandet, Paul Ambrose (Box 6, Folder 673)
        - Bigard, Jeanna and Stephanie (Box 6, Folder 674)
        - Bill, Samuel A. (Box 6, Folder 675)
        - Brilliart, Julie (Box 6, Folder 676)
        - Bingham, Hiram and Sybil (Box 6, Folder 677)
        - Bingham, Hiram Jr. (Box 6, Folder 678)
        - Bingham, Roland Victor (Box 6, Folder 679)
        - Bird, Mark Baker (Box 6, Folder 680)
        - Bird, Mary (Box 6, Folder 681)
        - Bird, William Wilberforce (Box 7, Folder 682)
        - Birinus (Box 7, Folder 683)
        - Birkeli, Fridtjov (Box 7, Folder 684)
        - Birkeli, Otto Emil (Box 7, Folder 685)
        - Birraux, Joseph Marie (Box 7, Folder 686)
        - Bishop, Artemus (Box 7, Folder 687)
        - Bishop, Isabella Bird (Box 7, Folder 688)
        - Bishop, W. Howard (Box 7, Folder 689)
        - Bisseux, Isaac (Box 7, Folder 690)
        - Black, William (Box 7, Folder 691)
        - Blackmore, Sophia (Box 7, Folder 692)
        - Blackstone, William Eugene (Box 7, Folder 693)
        - Blanchet, Francois Norbert (Box 7, Folder 694)
        - Bliss, Anna (Box 7, Folder 695)
        - Bliss, Daniel (Box 7, Folder 696)
        - Bliss, Edwin Munsell (Box 7, Folder 697)
        - Bliss, Isaac Grout (Box 7, Folder 698)
        - Bliss, Kathleen (Moore) (Box 7, Folder 699)
        - Bloch-Hoell, Nils E. (Box 7, Folder 700)
        - Blumhardt, Christian Gottlieb (Box 7, Folder 701)
        - Blyden, Edward Wilmont (Box 7, Folder 702)
        - Boardman, George Dana (Box 7, Folder 703)
        - Boaz, Thomas (Box 7, Folder 704)
        - Boberg, Folke (Box 7, Folder 705)
        - Bodelschwingh, Friedrich Von (Box 7, Folder 706)
        - Bodding, Paul Olaf (Box 7, Folder 707)
        - Boer, Harry R. (Box 7, Folder 708)
        - Bogue, David (Box 7, Folder 709)
        - Bohler, Peter (Box 7, Folder 710)
        - Bohner, Heinrich (Box 7, Folder 711)
        - Bohnisch, Frederick (Box 7, Folder 712)
        - Boisemenu, Alain de (Box 7, Folder 713)